[Si-eun] I asked a favor.
I said to stop.
[students exclaiming]
[Su-ho] Nope, nope.
Let's not cross the line, hmm?
Enough is enough.
You next?
Me? Nah,
you just woke up a guardian angel.
[Si-eun] Unconditioned reflex.
An innate, automatic response
to a stimulus,
such as closing one's eyes unconsciously
when an object suddenly appears.
- [students exclaiming]
- [Su-ho] Damn it.
Cut it out, crazy man.
I'll have to hit you if you don't. Hmm?
[sighs] You should've stopped when I said.
Who are you to tell me what to do?
[tense music playing]
[teacher] What are you two doing?
[silence]
Put… put the chair down!
How could you even think
of doing this in class?
Let me explain, ma'am.
I was trying to break up
my friends' fight.
But then, I almost fell over this chair.
I'm really sorry.
[sighs] Apologize to her.
Come on, hurry!
[gentle ambient music playing]
[Si-eun breathing heavily]
[breathing echoing]
["Hero" by Meego playing]
WEAK HERO:
CLASS 1
[siren blaring]
JEONGJIN SEOUL HOSPITAL
[teacher] Yes.
We just got to the hospital.
Yes, I'll talk to her.
Please don't worry.
I'll call you later.
[woman] You're here by yourself?
- I'm sorry, ma'am. Please calm down.
- I told you to bring your mom.
So why did you show up alone?
- I apologize.
- Bring your mom. Don't apologize instead.
I don't have one.
[scoffs] Oh, I don't believe you.
Listen, I am going to make sure you get
put into a detention center. Got it?
[tense music playing]
Today, Yeong-bin made another student
stick this on my neck.
[mother] What is that?
Ah, well, it's…
A narcotic. Drugs.
[Yeong-bin] You're fucking lying.
Where's your proof? Do you have
evidence that I fucking did it?
You're really unobservant, aren't you?
- Isn't this your backpack?
- [unzips]
FENTANYL PATCHES
[teacher] You do understand,
addressing the fight isn't the issue here.
Yeong-bin will need to be transferred
to another school.
If this were to be publicized, it would…
It's best to let it go quietly.
[mother sighs]
[door lock keypad bleeping]
[TV playing softly]
[bleeping]
[father] There's my kid.
Si-eun-a, what happened to your hand?
Oh, I got hurt during PE.
[father] Let me see.
You didn't faint again, did you?
No, I haven't in a while.
You punk. Are you…
getting into fights now? Is that it?
It's fine if you are.
It's almost like
a rite of passage for guys.
I've been there myself, too.
It's not like that.
[father] So, did you… get a good punch in?
Huh?
- [sighs]
- All right, I won't pry. Get rest.
Must be puberty.
[pensive ambient music playing]
[sighs]
- [boy 1] What are you doing?
- [boy 2] I told you not…
[boy 2] Okay. All right, that's fine.
[papers rustling]
[whispering] Yeah, I think there's
something seriously wrong with…
[tense music playing]
[chair clatters]
Hey, shitball.
See me after school.
[Tae-hun] You caught me off guard
yesterday, you loser.
But I'll fucking kill you today.
[closes book]
[slams pen down]
Why don't you see me now?
[sighs] I am sick of this.
- [Tae-hun] I can't believe this asshole.
- [boy 3] Should we follow them?
Are they going to fight?
- Yeah.
- Shouldn't we go stop them or something?
- Let's go!
- [all murmuring]
This is gonna be wild.
I told you…
[nervy music playing]
[excited conversations continue]
[Tae-hun] I owe him a teachable lesson.
- [door slams]
- [music stops]
[Tae-hun] Oh shit.
[silence]
[Si-eun] I guess
you guys are pretty stupid, aren't you?
- What the hell did you call us?
- Ugh. This guy.
[boy 4] No, but why did he make them
follow him into the bathroom?
[students gasping]
[Jeong-chan] What is he doing?
[Si-eun] You need a review…
since your memory's bad.
[clicks]
[Si-eun] Pavlov's dog experiment.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Si-eun] Ring the bell.
[pen clicks]
[Si-eun] Feed the dog.
[Si-eun] The dog salivates.
Ring the bell.
[pen clicks]
- [Si-eun] Feed the dog.
- [pen clicks]
[Si-eun] The dog salivates.
[clicks]
[Si-eun] Just ring the bell.
No more of this.
Do me a favor.
I'm asking
to stop.
- [music stops]
- [clicks]
[Tae-hun breathing shakily]
[door opens]
[door closes]
- What's going on with them?
- They were just standing in the bathroom.
Hey, Si-eun, what happened in there?
Did you show those assholes
what's up, again?
- Right!
- [boy 1] Wait. Let's see what he says.
I wanna hear it from his mouth.
He's gonna tell us what happened.
Do I know you?
[boy 2] That was harsh.
Are we close?
- [boy 3] That was…
- [boy 4] I almost did it.
Dang. He is kind of badass, though.
Not gonna lie.
[sighs]
[birdsong]
[quiet, tense music playing]
[Su-ho sighs]
What's going on? Where is everybody?
[PA chimes]
[muffled announcement on PA]
You didn't listen to what I said.
What's this?
[can opens]
[dealer] Get a nose job,
since you're here.
[quiet, menacing music playing]
Who is he?
Guy in my class.
How much will you pay?
How much do you want?
[scoffs] Are you made of fucking money?
I should've been your dad's son
instead of nephew.
"Help me,
hyeong."
Say it.
"Help me, hyeong."
[sighs]
Help me,
hyeong.
[horn honking]
Hey! What are you doin' here?
Were we married in a past life?
Anyway, where are you goin'?
Me? Home.
What?
Home.
After hagwon?
- Yeah.
- [Su-ho] Oh.
I'm sorry.
Are ya?
You can buy me a meal
if you wanna apologize.
Oh, the light. See you around.
[motorbike accelerates away]
["Home Sick" by Benzamin plays]
These for me?
Delivery!
Hello? Delivery.
[lock bleeps]
[doorbell rings]
Delivery.
- Hey, do you want some candy?
- Yeah.
Don't tell anyone. Sh!
[bleeps]
[dog barking]
♪ Baby, I don't know how to go home
Now I'm sick… ♪
[song continues in Korean]
[sighs]
BYUKSAN HIGH SCHOOL
FACULTY SHOWER ROOM
[Su-ho snoring]
[song ends]
[snoring]
Hmm?
- Time for lunch.
- [Su-ho sighs] Mmph.
Mmm. Ah, I'm good.
- [grunts]
- [Si-eun] You wanted me to treat.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I won't eat.
[cheering and clapping outside]
[quirky music playing]
I wasn't asking you
to buy something expensive,
but I can pay for my own school lunch.
Then don't eat it.
[sighs] I'll eat it.
[Si-eun] By the way,
why do you sleep here?
Oh, I come here after my part-time job.
If I went home,
I wouldn't wake up on time.
My grandma said
it's okay not to go to college,
but I have to have perfect attendance
and my high school diploma.
[slurps]
Are you music obsessed or something?
You're always wearing earbuds.
It's kind of rude, bro.
- And convenient.
- What?
It's to prevent people
from trying to talk to me.
You're a freakin' weirdo, you know that?
Might want to look in the mirror.
[chuckling]
Oh.
Hey, why isn't Yeon Si-eun
getting reprimanded?
I heard that Jeon Yeong-bin
was caught with fucking fentanyl.
- [all gasp]
- Really?
No way.
It's legit. They're not punishing him
so he doesn't talk.
But why all of a sudden
are they hanging out together?
I don't know. Out of nowhere,
they became best friends.
[boy 1] I heard Ahn Su-ho is freaking good
at MMA. He almost debuted in the AFC.
[boy 2] I knew it.
His counterpunch was fucking awesome!
[laughter]
HERO CASINO
PURCHASE GAME MONEY
PLAYER - TIE - BANKER
[moody music playing]
BET
[chiming]
LOSE
[groans]
[dealer] Stamp here, here, and here.
PROMISSORY NOTE
[papers rustling]
[girl] Oh! Gucci.
Nice bag.
Where's the label?
CREDITOR: JEON SEOK-DAE
DEBTOR: KIM WON-SEOK
It's on. Awesome.
When… are you gonna wire the money?
Go.
[associate 1] That deal went
so fucking smooth. Smooth.
- [Yeong-bin] You're late.
- Yeah.
I'm not sorry.
[lighter clicks]
- Crop this one…
- [Seok-dae] Say hi to the kids.
He's my cousin.
He's rich.
What?
What do you want?
You look like shit, dude.
Who, me?
- [laughing]
- Man, that's fuckin' rough.
- [Yeong-bin] Me?
- [girl] Asshole.
- [associate 1] Fuckin' nice.
- [Yeong-bin] Anyway.
[Seok-dae] Hey.
When's he get out?
[Beom-seok] Si-eun.
Si-eun.
You don't have to stay for night study?
[Si-eun] Hagwon?
[sighs] Yeah.
[Beom-seok] Which hagwon do you go to?
Daemyeong.
[Beom-seok] I'm thinking about
going to a hagwon too.
Do you like yours? Should I go there?
You don't have to get on my good side.
I won't accept your apology either.
[boy 1] Let's get this over with.
[boy 2] Bye! See you guys.
I'll wait for you outside.
- [Su-ho yells] Yah! Come on!
- [boy 3] Oh shit!
[exhales] You scared me.
What's going on? School's done?
[boy 4 scoffs] Yeah.
[Su-ho sighs] Why do you guys
have to hurt my feelings?
- Nobody woke me up.
- You said for us not to.
[all chuckle]
I did?
Can you wake me up in ten?
[sighs]
[birdsong]
[tense music playing]
This guy?
[sighs] This is bullshit.
You're not embarrassed? It won't be fair.
I have to go to my hagwon.
Nothing personal.
It's just business.
- [murmuring]
- Hey, isn't that Jeon Yeong-bin?
Looking for a fight.
- Have you seen her before?
- Looks like it.
[boy] Oh shit.
[Su-ho snoring]
[tense music continues]
[Beom-seok] Hey, Su-ho.
- [snoring]
- Ahn Su-ho.
That asshole Yeong-bin
took Si-eun somewhere.
[sighs] What?
- I said Yeong-bin took Si-eun somewhere.
- Yeah, and?
What? You should help him, Su-ho.
Don't you think so?
Didn't you do martial arts?
We're not really that close, you know.
Okay, but how close
do you have to be to help him?
[yawns] Go tell the homeroom teacher
to help him. I have work.
- [grunts]
- How about if I pay you?
I'll pay you double.
My pleasure. All right.
[upbeat pop music playing]
[Su-ho] At your service. Let's go.
[bleeping]
Get on! Here.
Keep an eye out.
[music stops]
[lighter clicks]
Yeong-i, go keep watch.
Wow.
I'm seriously bored out of my mind.
You're acting like a bunch of kids.
Gil-su's calling. Be quick.
[scoffs] So stupid.
[Yeong-bin] His hands.
Break his hands into pieces.
He'll never study again.
[tense music playing]
[Si-eun] Three on the left.
Take care of them first.
Two on the right move
on conditioned reflex. Handle them later.
I have to get a head start.
Let's get it over with.
Nice try.
- [Seok-dae] Whoa!
- Oh shit.
[yelping]
[groaning]
You fuck…
[associate 1 yells]
[yelps]
[Si-eun grunts]
[associate 2 grunts]
Eat shit.
[grunts]
[yells]
[music stops]
[all sighing and groaning]
[associate 2] Oh shit. [grunts]
[sighs]
Move it.
[both sigh]
Hey.
[tense music playing]
[Seok-dae] My bad.
I thought you were weak.
[running footsteps]
Hey, get out of my way.
You asshole! Fuck you, bro.
Fuck you! Shithead!
Psycho! You staring fucking psycho!
Fuck you, you… Fuck! Fuck!
Fuck! Fucker!
Hey, come grab his hand.
Let's fuck him up.
- Come here.
- [Si-eun panting]
[Tae-hun] You can't leave, shithead.
Not yet.
Happy studying!
[Si-eun groaning]
[laughs]
Know your place, asshole.
You shouldn't have even
messed with me, you shithead.
[running footsteps]
[panting] Should you?
- Whoo!
- [Jeong-chan] You okay, Yeong-bin-a?
- [associate 2] Who the hell is that?
- [coughing]
[associate 1] No idea, dude.
Are you okay?
[Si-eun gasping]
Ugh. My arm hurts.
You can stop now. Okay?
[menacing music playing]
[Seok-dae] Hey.
[Su-ho] Oh!
[Seok-dae] Asshole.
Hey. Go get that fucking bitch.
[Tae-hun] You bitch!
You're sick!
Die, motherfucker!
- [Su-ho] Tap out already.
- [Seok-dae grunts]
- [Su-ho] Otherwise you're gonna die.
- [Yeong-bin] Hey, move!
My shit…
Fucker!
[Su-ho grunts]
[Seok-dae groans]
- Hey!
- [grunts]
On your--
- [thud]
- [music stops]
- [Yeong-bin groans]
- [bottle clatters]
[all panting]
Oh shit.
- Shithead.
- [Seok-dae] Nice hit, bro.
[Su-ho] Hah!
All you guys,
aren't you embarrassed
about ganging up on him?
If it were me, I'd die of humiliation.
[Yeong-bin] Hyeong.
What's up?
- What's next?
- [sighs] Hi there.
[sighs]
[Seok-dae sighs]
[Su-ho] Your hyeong must be embarrassed.
Let's call it a day.
Look, he's leaving.
[Yeong-i] Hey, Gil-su called.
- [scoffs]
- [associate 1] Hey, let's go.
- [Yeong-i grunts]
- Ow.
- [Yeong-i] Huh? Huh?
- [associate 2 sighs]
[Si-eun] Jeon Yeong-bin.
Enough.
Just stop.
[sighs]
[Su-ho] Let's go.
- Ah. Ooh.
- [Beom-seok] You okay?
[Su-ho] Let me see.
- You're pretty scraped up, huh?
- [Si-eun] Stop.
[yawns]
Aah, I'm hungry after doing all that.
Let's go eat.
I know an awesome place we can go.
Time to pay your bill. Hmm?
[bleeping]
[starts engine]
What? Hop on.
- I have hagwon.
- [Su-ho] Come on.
We came to your rescue. That's all we get?
You're not even going to thank us?
This place is really good.
[sighs]
[sizzling]
[cutlery scraping]
It's on me today. Really.
I'm sorry I'm late, Emo.
[Emo] You're here. You're very late.
- [Su-ho] Yes.
- [Emo] Did you eat?
- [Su-ho] I'll eat later. Okay?
- [Emo] You must've had a tough day.
Hey, I'm late because of you guys.
So help out.
- [Emo] Are these your friends?
- Uh-huh. Oh, hello.
[country music playing]
[Su-ho] Hey, make sure
you make it sparkle, okay?
[Emo] Oh! You're so thorough
at washing dishes!
Your mom must adore you.
You're such a wonderful boy. [chuckles]
[Su-ho] Hey, grab the last box.
[man] It's okay. It's okay.
I got it.
- Do you work two jobs every day?
- [Su-ho] What?
I only deliver food three days a week.
Not every day.
Isn't it hard?
It's no big deal.
I work for a moving company on weekends.
[man] Dude, no. Milk and ham go together.
[Su-ho] Why?
Do I seem too mature to you? Or what?
- [chuckles]
- [chairs scrape]
[Su-ho] Oh, hello, welcome. Yes.
Finish the rest.
What can I get you?
Take your time and let me know.
[man] Hey, can we get some more glasses?
[Beom-seok clears throat]
Um…
Um, about the mock test.
I'm, uh… I'm sorry.
Uh… Jeon Yeong-bin threatened me.
I had no idea that it was… what it was.
I know.
It's fine.
Mmm.
[Su-ho] Aah, I'm starving.
- [Si-eun]Yeah.
- [Su-ho] Aah!
Mmm!
- Mmm.
- Is it better that way?
Mmm.
I'll try it.
[chuckles]
- It's killer, yeah?
- [Beom-seok, mouth full] It's hot.
So hot. [laughs]
[upbeat music playing]
[Su-ho] Well, dear Si-eun-ssi, wanna try?
Meat's always better when you stuff
your mouth and eat it in one bite.
You can have it.
Aw.
Hey. No one's ever lost anything
from listening to me.
So come on now.
Mmm? "Aah."
Are your hands clean?
What the…
This guy has no idea.
Food tastes better this way. All right?
It's okay. "Aah. Aah!"
Yeah? "Aah!"
[Si-eun] Ah.
[Su-ho] "Aah!"
It's good? Awesome, right?
[chuckles]
Right?
- [Beom-seok] This meat is amazing.
- [Su-ho] See?
- Come whenever.
- [phone buzzes]
- [Beom-seok] Can I really?
- [Su-ho] Yeah.
[music fades]
FATHER: WHERE ARE YOU?
DIDN'T YOU GO TO NIGHT STUDY?
[man] Uh-huh. How are yours?
SU-HO, THAT WAS SO TASTY
LET'S GO AGAIN SOMETIME
SU-HO, FOLLOW ME BACK ON INSTAGRAM
[knuckles cracking]
[pop music playing on video]
[man on video] There are many people
who take on a challenging job,
only to quit soon after
because it doesn't suit them.
Don't get too caught up
in your credentials.
If you continue to work
hard in your field,
I know that you'll find many opportunities
to make money here in Korea.
DELIVERY ORDER
I'm in the real estate industry right now,
but if I--
[stops video]
[sighs]
[grunts]
[Si-eun's mother] Next, why don't we talk
about indefinite equations?
Indefinite equations are
the very core of all advanced mathematics.
This concept is primarily used
across all of mathematics' areas,
so we'll be going over it in detail today.
Now, indefinite equations.
What exactly do we call
an indefinite equation?
"In" and "definite." These together
mean an undetermined equation.
Why is it undetermined?
Well, that's because
there are multiple possible answers,
and it is difficult to point to one
of them and know, "This is the answer."
So let's try to define
this indefinite equation mathematically.
When we compare the number of unknowns
and the number of equations,
the number of unknowns is
greater than the number of equations,
which leads us to know that…
[gentle, pensive music playing]
[man] Hey, fucker.
[music slows]
[man] Who was it?
[music becomes dramatic]
[moody electronic music playing]
ALL NAMES, PLACES, AND EVENTS
ARE FICTIONAL
ANY SIMILARITY TO REALITY IS COINCIDENTAL